{
    "subject": "resource/Dicobalt_octacarbonyl",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Dicobalt octacarbonyl",
    "human_readable": "The name of Dicobalt octacarbonyl is Dicobalt octacarbonyl.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9836558103561401,
            "question": "What is the name of Dicobalt octacarbonyl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9669983386993408,
            "question": "Is Dicobalt octacarbonyl its own name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9290170669555664,
            "question": "What are some alternative names for Dicobalt octacarbonyl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8941923379898071,
            "question": "Does Dicobalt octacarbonyl refer to a specific compound?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8637180924415588,
            "question": "How is Dicobalt octacarbonyl synthesized?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8547492027282715,
            "question": "What are some common uses for Dicobalt octacarbonyl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8483302593231201,
            "question": "Where can I find more detailed information about Dicobalt octacarbonyl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.791193425655365,
            "question": "Could you provide more information about the chemical structure of Dicobalt octacarbonyl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7644996047019958,
            "question": "Is Dicobalt octacarbonyl used in any specific industries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7175619602203369,
            "question": "Are there any hazards associated with Dicobalt octacarbonyl?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Dicobalt octacarbonyl is Dicobalt octacarbonyl.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4241_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Dicobalt octacarbonyl used in any specific industries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4241_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you provide more information about the chemical structure of Dicobalt octacarbonyl?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4241_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I find more detailed information about Dicobalt octacarbonyl?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4241_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4241_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that \"The name of Dicobalt octacarbonyl is Dicobalt octacarbonyl.\" Each document refers to this compound as \"Dicobalt octacarbonyl\" and lists it under various headings, confirming its name."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}